export const quesDataArr = [
  {
    question: "There are ___ levels of heading in HTML",
    answers: ["three", "four", "five", "six"],
    rightAns: "six",
  },
  {
    question:
      "The decimal range of network address for class B network is between",
    answers: ["127-190", "128-190", "128-191", "None of the above"],
    rightAns: "128-191",
  },
  {
    question: "What is the Full Form of the SPX",
    answers: [
      "sequenced packet exchange",
      "sequence packet exchange",
      "sequenced packets exchange",
      "none of the above",
    ],
    rightAns: "sequenced packet exchange",
  },
  {
    question: "What is the Full Form of the IMAP",
    answers: [
      "Internet Mail Access Protocol",
      "Internet Mails Access Protocol",
      "Internet Memo Access Protocol",
      "All of the above",
    ],
    rightAns: "Internet Mail Access Protocol",
  },
  {
    question: "The Full form Of the MIME is:",
    answers: [
      "Multipurpose Internet Mail Extensions",
      "Multiple Internet Mail Extensions",
      "Multiple Internet Mails Extensions",
      "none of the above",
    ],
    rightAns: "Multipurpose Internet Mail Extensions",
  },
  {
    question:
      "The ___ at the bottom of your window provides you the status of how much percentage of the Web Page is loaded and how much is remaining.",
    answers: [
      "Program Indicator",
      "Program Director",
      "Progress Indicator",
      "none of the above",
    ],
    rightAns: "Progress Indicator",
  },
  {
    question: "The Major components of the Web browser are ___",
    answers: ["Menu bar", "Toolbar", "Location", "All of the above"],
    rightAns: "All of the above",
  },
  {
    question: "__ is widely known as the father of the World Wide Web",
    answers: [
      "Tom burners-lee",
      "Tom bruce-lee",
      "Tim Berners-Lee",
      "Tim bruce-lee",
    ],
    rightAns: "Tim Berners-Lee",
  },
  {
    question: "We can test our web pages through:",
    answers: [
      "Using Photoshop",
      "Using Dreamweaver",
      "Using Flash",
      "All of the above",
    ],
    rightAns: "Using Dreamweaver",
  },
  {
    question: "URL is an acronym for -",
    answers: [
      "Uniform resource locator",
      "Universal resource locator",
      "Uniform research locator",
      "Universal research locator",
    ],
    rightAns: "Uniform resource locator",
  },
];
